(Penny:)It'll be like
the weirdest Comic-Con ever.
(Sheldon:)I know that you worked hard
to put this together.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry I'm ruining it.
(Adam West:)Oh, pl...
You're not ruining it.
(Penny:)Look, at some point,
Raj will try to get everyone
(Penny:)to do the Electric Slide.
(Penny:)Now, that will ruin it.
(Sheldon:)I don't think
I can go back out there.
(Penny:)That's fine.
(Penny:)You know, I hate that
your sister and her friends
(Penny:)used to torture you.
(Penny:)But what I hate even more
(Penny:)is, if I was there,
I would have tortured you, too.
(Sheldon:)Based on this pep talk,
I'd say you're still doing it.
(scoffs)
My point is,
(Penny:)there was a time I never
would've been friends
(Penny:)with someone like you,
and now...
(Penny:)you are one
of my favorite people.
(Penny:)So, if what you need is